

Sergi Palau Tort

Full Stack software engineer with background in electronics engineering.

Leader of small teams working in different languages, frameworks, libraries and cms, experienced in JavaScript, always keen to learn

More than 5 years of work experience creating websites, web and mobile apps, e-commerce, payment gateway and APIs.

I love to see how lines of code become amazing things.

10-01-1983 (i)

Barcelona 💡

605240485

hi@sergipt.com ⊠

https://sergipt.com/

https://github.com/sergipt/

https://linkedin.com/in/sergipt/ in



SKILLS

JavaScript, Node.js, React, React native, Koa, Express, Angular, MongoDb, SQL, Redis, Git, API development, PHP, Java, HTML5, SASS, CSS3.

EXPERIENCE

2011 - 2017Full stack developer

Verdelimón

Website, web app and e-comerce development

2015 - 2015Web developer

Paack

Shipping platform development

2009 - 2010**Telecommunications management**

Abertis Telecom

Management of radio links, routers and telecommunications systems

2009 - 2009**Junior IT**

Acieroid

Network management

2008 - 2008Junior developer and analyst

Mesure Systems

MES and MOM systems implementation

2007 - 2008**Presale support**

Siemens Enterprise Communications

Modular communications platform technical design

EDUCATION

2017 - 2018Codeworks

Full Stack software Engineer

2001 - 2008**EUSS**

Electronic engineering

LANGUAGES & OTHERS

Català - Castellano - English

Drive license and vehicle